Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection
Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection
- Photographs
  - Kings Row, 4/1/1956; 2627; 7x9; includes caption; Leslie, Nan (Box 5)
  - Kings Row, 9/13/1955; 2628; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Kelly, Jack; Horton, Robert; Leshe, Nan (Box 5)
  - Kirby, Diane, 2023; 8x10, good condition (Box 5)
  - Kirby, Diane, 2044; 8x10, good condition (Box 5)
  - Kitty Foyle, 1/17/1958; 2447; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Murray, Kathleen (Box 5)
  - Kozlow, Bucky, 2045; 8x10, good condition (Box 5)
  - Kraft Music Hall, 4/15/1956; 2232; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Como, Perry; Genevieve (Box 6)
  - Kraft Music Hall, 2280; 7xg, poor condition; includes caption; Hope, Bob; Como, Perry (Box 6)
  - Kraft Music Hall, 10/4/1956; 2402; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Yankees (Baseball team); Como, Perry (Box 6)
  - Kraft Music Hall: Milton Berle, 12/3/1958; 2450; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Fitzgerald, Ella; Berle, Milton (Box 6)
  - Kraft Mystery Theatre, 6/14/1958; 1936; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption (Box 6)
  - Kraft Mystery Theatre: Shadow of a Man, 6/4/1963; 2494; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Kelly, Jack; Owen, Beverly (Box 6)
  - Kraft Mystery Theatre: Talk to my Partner, 2279; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Moore, Joanna (Box 6)
  - Laffan, Patricia, 2562; 6x8, good condition (Box 6)
  - Land, 2/9/1962; 2581; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Huntley, Chet (Box 6)
  - Laramie, 9/15/1959; 2227; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Crawford, Bobby, Jr. (Box 6)
  - Laramie: Dark Verdict, 11/24/1959; 2525; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Mitchell, Thomas (Box 6)
  - Laramie: Renegade Brand, 2/26/1963; 2652; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Patrick, Lory; Nolan, Jean (Box 6)
  - Lawman: Deputy, 2191; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Brown, Peter (Box 6)
  - Lawrence Welk Show, 1967; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption (Box 6)
  - Lawrence Welk Show, 5/20/1958; 2169; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; upper right corner missing; Lennon, Diane (Box 6)
  - Lerner & Loewe, Broadway's Last Romantics, 3/10/1988; 1483; 10x8, excellent condition; Bobby Hansson, photographer; Hepburn, Audrey; Kiley, Richard (Box 6)
  - Lerner & Loewe, Broadway's Last Romantics, 1522; 8x10, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Loewe, Frederick; Lerner, Alan J. (Box 6)
  - Lerner & Loewe: Broadways' Last Romantics, 1526; 10x8, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet; PBS Television Network; Andrews, Julie; Harrison, Rex; Hepburn, Audrey; My Fair Lady (Musical) (Box 6)
  - Let's Make a Deal (game show), 12/5/1963; 2613; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Hall, Monty; Merrill, Carol (Box 6)
  - Lewis, Brenda, 2511; 8x10, poor condition; Girl in Pink Tights, The (Musical) (Box 6)
  - Liberace Show, 2411; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Liberace, George; Liberace, Wladziu (Walter) Valentino (Box 6)
  - Liberace Show, 9/25/1958; 2456; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Liberace, Wladziu (Walter) Valentino (Box 6)
  - Life of Riley, 9/21/1953; 2358; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Bendix, William (Box 6)
  - Life of Riley, 4368; 10x8, good condition; Bendix, William; DeCamp, Rosemary; Rees, Lanny; Winters, Gloria (Box 6)
  - Life of Riley: Juvenile Delinquent, 10/17/1956; 2499; 10x8, fair/average condition; includes caption; Morgan, Wesley; Bendix, William (Box 6)
  - Life of Riley: Movie Struck, 1/31/1958; 2435; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Bendix, Lorraine; Montgomery, George; Hitchcock, Patricia (Box 6)
  - Life of Riley: Riley and the Foreman's Gift, 5/7/1954; 2393; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Bendix, William; Parnell, Emory (Box 6)
  - Live from the Met: Jessye Norman, 1/27/1988; 1489; 5x7, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Norman, Jessye (Box 6)
  - Living Single: The Shakeup, 5/18/1995; 2735; 8x10, excellent condition; Fields, Kim (Box 6)
  - Lone Ranger, 2291; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; depicts the Lone Ranger with children; Wrather, Linda; Wrather, Jack; Ladd, David; Wrather, Chris; Granville, Bonita; Trilling, Susan; Moore, Clayton; Wrather, Molly (Box 6)
  - Look Up and Live: Shadow of the Valley, 3/3/1963; 2330; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Poole, Roy; Madden, Donald (Box 6)
  - Look Up and Live: Shadow of the Valley, 3/3/1963; 2401; 10x8, fair/average condition; includes caption; Scollay, Fred; Holland, Betty Lou; Madden, Donald; Poole, Roy (Box 6)
  - Lorenzo Jones, 11/12/1954; 2427; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Raby, John; NBC Radio (Box 6)
  - Loud Red Patrick, 10/3/1956; 2569; 8x10, very poor condition; Wayne, David (Box 6)
  - Loud Red Patrick, 2570; 8xl0, very poor condition; Congdon, James; Wayne, David (Box 6)
  - Loud Red Patrick, 2571; 8xl0, very poor condition; Kennedy, Arthur; Wayne, David (Box 6)
  - Love That Jill: They Went Thataway, 1939; 7x9, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Janssen, Eileen (Box 6)
  - Lux Video Theatre: Night Song, 1/18/1956; 1962; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Scully, Francis; Rush, Barbara; Contino, Dick (Box 6)
  - Lux Video Theatre: The Queen’s English, 5/13/1954; 2174; 8x10, poor condition; Notes on back; Harding, Ann (Box 6)
  - Lux Video Theatre: The Queen’s English, 5/30/1954; 2740; 8x10, poor condition; Harding, Ann (Box 6)
  - Make Room for Daddy (The Danny Thomas Show), 2590; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Hamer, Rusty; Jackson, Shirley; Hagen, Jean (Box 6)
  - Man and the Challenge: Escape to Nepal, 1948; 4x5, poor condition; Accompanies larger photo of Ray Milland; Nader, George; Granville, Joan (Box 6)
  - Man from U.N.C.L.E., 2335; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Heatherly, May (Box 6)
  - Married With Children: The Bundys in London, 5/3/1992; 2737; 8x10, excellent condition; Applegate, Christina; O'Neil, Ed; Sagal, Katey; Faustino, David (Box 6)
  - Masquerade Party (game show), 12/9/1956; 2614; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hall Healy, Mary (Box 6)
  - Masquerade Party, 12/21/1955; 2317; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Donald, Peter; Parker, Fess (Box 6)
  - Massine, Leonide, 2022; 8x10, poor condition (Box 6)
  - Masterpiece Theatre:, 1515; 8x10, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet: Day After the Fair and Fortunes of Wai; PBS Television Network; Gordon, Hannah; Branagh, Kenneth (Box 6)
  - Maverick: Passage to Fort Doom, 8/23/1959; 2606; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Howell, Arlene; Kelly, Jack (Box 6)
  - Maverick: Rope of Cards, 1946; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Marshall, Joan (Box 6)
  - Max Liebman's Color Spectacular, 2463; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Holliday, Judy (Box 6)
  - McGreedy, Robert M., 2039; 8x10, good condition; Fabian Bachrach, photographer; Television Advertising Representatives, Inc. (Box 6)
  - McZnikoff, Marvin D., 2059; 2 items 8 x10, good condition (Box 6)
  - Mead, Julia, 2020; 10x8, fair/average condition (Box 6)
  - Medallion Theatre: Mrs. Union Station, 7/23/1953; 2431; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Havoc, June (Box 6)
  - Medical Horizons, 1990; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Krugman, Saul; Bellevue Hospital (Box 6)
  - Medical Horizons, 9/12/1955; 2536; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Howe, Quincy (Box 6)
  - Meet Mille, 10/25/1952; 2563; 8x10, poor condition; Halop, Florence (Box 6)
  - Mehlig, Lee, 2060; 8x10, good condition; includes caption on back; Blair Radio (Box 6)
  - Melody Tour, 2226; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Fisher, Nelle (Box 6)
  - Mendelsohn, Alfred L., 2101; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; EUE/Screen Gems (Box 6)
  - Mendelson, 2054; 8x10, good condition (Box 6)
  - Mergener, Philip, 2061; 8x10, good condition (Box 6)
  - Metcalfe, Edwin C., 2073; 5x7, good condition (Box 6)
  - Meterpaul, Stephen C., 2058; 8x10; Robert E. Eastman and Company, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Metropolitan Opera: La Forza del Destino, 1/14/1958; 2400; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Roggero, Margaret (Box 6)
  - Metropolitan Opera: Vanessa, 1/22/1958; 2459; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Elias, Rosalind; Barber, Samuel; Menotti, Gian-Carlo (Box 6)
  - Meyer, Walter, 2051; 8x10, good condition; Oak Electro/Netics Corp.; Oak Manufacturing Co.; TV Turner Advance Development Laboratory (Box 6)
  - Meyers, 2056; 8x10, good condition; WGN (Television station) (Box 6)
  - MGM Parade: Tribute to a Bad Man, 2319; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption (Box 7)
  - Michaels, Pat, 10/23/1963; 2063; 4x5, good condition; KBLA (Los Angeles, Ca.) (Box 7)
  - Middendorf, Donald G., 12/18/1964; 2066; 8x10, good condition; Donald G. Crosley Broadcasting Corp. (Box 7)
  - Miller, Alan B. Jr., 2062; 8x10, good condition; includes caption on back; Ted Bales and Company, Inc.; Miller, Alan B. Jr. (Box 7)
  - Miller, D. Thomas, 2053; 8x10, good condition (Box 7)
  - Miller, Frank, 2071; 8x10, good condition (Box 7)
  - Miller, Paul, 2070; 4.5x7, good condition; Associated Press; Garnett Company (Rochester, N.Y.) (Box 7)
  - Miller, Thomas, 2064; 8x10, good condition (Box 7)
  - Miller, William, 2057; 8x10, good condition (Box 7)
  - Mills, Delbert, 2067; 8x10 2 items, good condition; RCA (Box 7)
  - Milner, 2069; 8x10, good condition; WTAC (Radio station) (Box 7)
  - Minelli, Liza, 2125; 8x10, extremely poor condition (Box 7)
  - Miner, Peter, 2055; 8x10, good condition (Box 7)
  - Miss America Beauty Pageant, 9/11/1955; 2362; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Myerson, Bess; Daly, John (Box 7)
  - Missing Links (game show), 8/30/1963; 2421; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; McMahon, Ed; Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson (Television program) (Box 7)
  - Misterly, Frank S., 2068; 8x10, good condition; RCA (Box 7)
  - Mitchell, Robert D., 2065; 8x10 (Box 7)
  - Mitchell, T. E., 2052; 8x10, good condition (Box 7)
  - Mix, Shirley, 2072; 5x7, good condition; KTVB (Box 7)
  - Monday Night at the Movies: King of the Khyber Rifles, 6/17/1968; 2650; 9x7, very poor condition; includes caption; Power, Tyrone; Sujata (Box 7)
  - Moore, Terry, 2567; 8x10, poor condition (Box 7)
  - Motorola TV Hour: The Brandenburg Gate, 11/23/1953; 2327; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Riva, Maria; Palance, Jack (Box 7)
  - Mr. Citizen: Second Class Citizen, 2256; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Bush, William; Horn, Sandy; Bayless, Anita (Box 7)
  - Munro, Craddock, 2198; 10x8, good condition; Includes biographical information and resume on back; 6 photos on sheet; My Three Angels; Pygmalion; Merchant of Venice; Schlitz Theatre (Television program); I Was a Male War Bride (Motion picture); Lady in the Dark; Dark of the Moon; Peg O'My Heart; Legend of Lovers (Box 7)
  - Murphy, Audie, 2504; 4.25x3.5, good condition (Box 7)
  - Murphy, Mary, 2262; 8x10, poor condition (Box 7)
  - Murray, Ken, 2654; 7x9, good condition (Box 7)
  - Murrow, Edward, 2716; 7x9, good condition; Murrow, Edward R. (Box 7)
  - Music for a Summer Night: Female of the Species, 2469; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Fitzgerald, Geraldine (Box 7)
  - Mutual Broadcasting, 2078; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 7)
  - My Favorite Husband, 8/25/1953; 2539; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Caulfield, Joan; Nelson, Barry (Box 7)
  - Mystery Time: The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes, 6/21/1956; 2483; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Gielgud, John, Sir (Box 7)
  - Mystery: The Silent World of Nicholas Quinn, 1507; 8x10, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Service of Ali the Dead; The Dead of Jericho; Thaw, John; Inspector Morse (Box 7)
  - N4asterpiece Theatre: David Copperfield, 1506; 8x10, excellent condition; Hurley, Colin; PBS Television Network (Box 7)
  - NAB (National Association of Broadcasters) Conference Registration, 1963; 2075; 10x8, good condition (Box 7)
  - NAB (National Association of Broadcasters) Convention, 2080; 10x8, fair/average condition; includes caption on back; Pack, Richard M; McGannon, Donald H.; Group W (Westinghouse Broadcasting Company) (Box 7)
  - Naish, J. Carol, 2024; 7x9, poor condition (Box 7)
  - Naked City: A Death of Princes, 10/12/1960; 2611; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Malone, Nancy (Box 7)
  - Naked City: The Human Trap, 1953; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Burke, Paul; O'Neill, Margaret (Box 7)
  - Naked City: The Pedigree Sheet, 10/9/1960; 2251; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Burke, Paul; Pleshette, Suzanne (Box 7)
  - Name That Tune, 6/19/1953; 1982; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Benson, Red; NBC Radio; Salter, Harry; Mills, Vicki (Box 7)
  - Name's the Same, 1956; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Alexander, Joan; Myerson, Bess; Stang, Arnold; Rayburn, Gene (Box 7)
  - National Farm and Home Hour, 7/30/1954; 1944; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; NBC Radio; Mitchell, Everett (Box 7)
  - Nature: Great Moments from Nature, Kingdom of the Ice Bear, In the Shadow of Fujisan, 1527; l0x8, excellent condition; Ian Stirling, photographer; 2 photos on sheet; PBS Television Network (Box 7)
  - Nature: Ducks in Flight, March 1988; 1488; 7x5, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Nature {Television program) (Box 7)
  - NBC Bandstand (Radio program), 8/2/1956; 2241; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Haymes, Dick; NBC Radio; Mr. Music (Box 7)
  - NBC Bandstand (Radio program), 2242; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Haymes, Dick; NBC Radio; Mr. Music (Box 7)
  - NBC Ceremony, 1/9/1964; 2087; 7x9; includes caption on back; Flynn, John M.; McKeon, Harry F.; Scott, Walter D.; Burholt, Robert; Carson, William; Kintner, Robert E.; Sarnoff, Robert W. (Box 7)
  - NBC Color City, 3/15/1955; 2547; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Television studios (Box 7)
  - NBC Color City, 3/15/1955; 2548; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Television studios (Box 7)
  - NBC Color City, 3/15/1955; 2549; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Lighting design and construction; Studios, Television (Box 7)
  - NBC Color City, 3/15/1955; 2550; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Television studios (Box 7)
  - NBC Color City, 3/15/1955; 2551; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Television studios (Box 7)
  - NBC Election Coverage (1960), 10/14/1960; 2011; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; McGee, Frank; Beatty, Morgan; Harkness, Richard C.; Vanocur, Sander; Mueller, Merrill; Chancellor, John; McCormick, Robert (Box 7)
  - NBC Film Documentary Unit: Murville and Salomon, 4/13/1955; 2336; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Saloman, Henry; Murville, Maurice Couve de; Victory at sea (Television program); Three, two, one, zero (Television program) (Box 7)
  - NBC Follies of 1965, 11/27/1965; 2190; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption, 4 pictures on sheet; Prowse, Juliet (Box 7)
  - NBC Matinee Theatre: Greybeards and Witches, 5/1/1956; 2464; 6x7, very poor condition; Includes partial caption; Moorehead, Agnes (Box 7)
  - NBC Opera Theatre: The Saint of Bleeker Street, 4/12/1955; 2379; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Aiken, David; Gerlando, Maria di; Copeland, Virginia; Cunningham, Davis (Box 7)
  - NBC Radio Programs: Today, Home, and Weekday, 3/14/1956; 2510; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Kelly, Grace; Rainier III, Prince of Monaco; Falkenburg, Jinx; Francis, Arlene; Markel, Hazel; Today (Radio program); Home (Radio program); Weekday (Radio program) (Box 7)
  - NBC Television Network, 2038; good condition; Includes picture of Frank Mullen; Mullen, Frank; Morton, Alfred H. (Box 7)
  - NBC White Paper, 11/11/1960; 2378; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; U-2 Incident, 1960; Powers, Francis Gary; NAC White Paper (Television program); U-2 (Reconnaissance aircraft) (Box 7)
  - NCAA Football Games, 9/15/1954; 2618; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Harmon, Tom (Box 7)
  - New Figures of 1957, 12/8/1957; 1965; 8x10, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Lucas, Jean; Chapman, Cecil (Box 7)
  - New Steve Allen Show, 1952; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Stewart, Sandy; Fountain, Pete (Box 7)
  - Nichols, Barbara, 2568; 7.5x9.5, fair/average condition (Box 7)
  - Nicol, Alex, 2474; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 7)
  - Nineteen Eighty-Four, 12/12/1954; 1988; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Cushing, Peter; BBC Television Service; 1984 (Novel); Morell, Andre; Mitchell, Yvonne (Box 7)
  - Nolan, Kathleen (Kathy), 2046; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 7)
  - NOVA, March 1988; 1477; l0x8, excellent condition; Amy Knowlton, photographer; PBS Television Network (Box 7)
  - NOVA: Top Gun and Beyond, 1497; 8x10, excellent condition; John Alexanders, photographer; F-16 fighter plane; PBS Television Network; Jet planes; Military (Box 7)
  - Novak, Kim, 2305; 8x10, fair/average condition; 5 Against the House (Motion picture) (Box 7)
  - NYPD Blue, 11/8/1994; 2845; 7x9, excellent condition; Franz, Dennis (Box 7)
  - Olmstead, Richard, 2370; 10x8, fair/average condition; includes caption; Olmstead Sound Studios; AIC Reverberation Unit (Box 7)
  - On Stage at Wolf Trap, 1514; 8x10, excellent condition; 4 photographs on sheet; Chieftains; Galway, James; McGovern, Maureen; Bennett, Tony; PBS Television Network (Box 7)
  - Original Amateur Hour, Lawrence Welk Show, 2397; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Mack, Ted (Box 7)
  - Our Miss Brooks, 11/17/1954; 1997; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; photographic sketch; Morgan, Jane; Curtis, Billy (Box 7)
  - Our Miss Brooks, 9/27/1955; 2195; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Arden, Eve; Sweeney, Bob (Box 7)
  - Our Miss Brooks, 3/10/1954; 2210; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Arden, Eve; Emmy Awards; Gordon, Gale (Box 7)
  - Our Miss Brooks, 4/20/1955; 2211; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Kearns, Joseph; Arden, Eve; Rockwell, Robert (Box 7)
  - Our Miss Brooks: The Auction, 2/25/1955; 2645; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Arden, Eve; Gordon, Gale (Box 7)
  - Outlaws, 8/1/1960; 2384; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Gaynor, Jock; Collier, Don; MacLane, Barton (Box 7)
  - OWL/TV / 1487, March 1988; 5x8, good condition; Derek Rodgers, photographer; PBS Television Network; Galapagos islands (Box 7)
  - Ozark Jubilee, 2351; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Wagoner, Porter; National Country Music Day; Haworth, Speedy; Warden, Don (Box 7)
  - Ozark Jubilee, 2492; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Warmwater, Luke (Box 7)
  - Paar, Jack, 2524; 5x7, fair/average condition; Jack Paar Show (Box 8)
  - Paar, Jack, 2553; 4x7, good condition (Box 8)
  - Packard Bell Home Products Division, 2094; 4x5, good condition; Includes press release about Packard Bell Sales Display Idea Award; Clover Furniture Company; Reedy, William; Bragg, Al; Kraus, Ralph; (Box 8)
  - Page, Patti, 2641; 8x10, poor condition (Box 8)
  - Paget, Debra, 2391; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 8)
  - Paget, Debra, 2417; 8x10, fair/average condition; Paramount Pictures (Box 8)
  - Paget, Debra, 2639; 8x10, poor condition; Twentieth-Century Fox Player (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Betsy, 2318; 8x10, very poor condition (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Betsy, 2367; 8xl0, poor condition (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Betsy, 2552; 4x4.5, good condition (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Buddy, 2505; 3.5x4.5, good condition (Box 8)
  - Pantomime Quiz, 1949; 8x10, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Stokey, Mike; Darcel, Denise (Box 8)
  - Pantomime Quiz, 1950; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Stokey, Susan Melissa; Stokey, Mike; Stokey, Spring (Box 8)
  - Pantomime Quiz, 1951; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Stokey, Mike; Darcel, Denise (Box 8)
  - Pantomime Quiz, 6/24/1954; 2245; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hart, Dorothy (Box 8)
  - Pantomime Quiz, 12/4/1953; 2321; 10x8, good condition; includes caption; Stritch, Elaine; Donnell, Jeff; Hart, Dorothy; Alda, Robert (Box 8)
  - Papp, Joseph "Joe" 1, 2320; 8x10, poor condition (Box 8)
  - Parker Four Star Playhouse: My Own Dear Dragon, 11/4/1954; 2006; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Miles, Vera; Boyer, Charles (Box 8)
  - Parker, Dean, 2312; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 8)
  - Pat Boone Chevy Showroom, 1978; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; O'Brien, Louise (Box 8)
  - Patrice Munsel Show, 2517; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Slezak, Walter (Box 8)
  - Patti Page Show, 6/13/1956; 2643; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Page, Patti (Box 8)
  - People and Other Animals, 2188; 8x10, good condition; Caption on back; Westinghouse Broadcasting Corporation (WBC); Morse, Robert; Fonda, Jane (Box 8)
  - People's Choice, 12/14/1955; 2185; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hansen, Myrna; Kickapoo Scout (Basset hound) (Box 8)
  - People's Choice, 12/14/1957; 2304; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Kilgas, Nancy (Box 8)
  - Pepper-Upper Time Starring Eydie Gorme, 3/26/1959; 2416; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption (Box 8)
  - Pepsi-Cola Playhouse: Passage Home, 4/7/1955; 2589; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Keith, Brian (Box 8)
  - Pepsi-Cola Playhouse: The Longest Legs in the Show, 5/1/1954; 2294; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; McCowan, Don (Box 8)
  - Peter Gunn, 2361; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Stevens, Craig (Box 8)
  - Peter Gunn: A Matter of Policy, 5/22/1961; 2299; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Navarro, Anna; Bernardi, Herschel; Stevens, Craig (Box 8)
  - Peter Gunn: The Ugly Frame, 7/24/1959; 2531; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Laine, Lari; Charles, Lewis; Stevens, Craig (Box 8)
  - Peter Loves Mary, 9/23/1960; 2258; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Langan, Glenn; Smith, Gil; Martin, Merry; Hayes, Peter Lind; Healy, Mary (Box 8)
  - Peters, Jean, 2419; 8x10, poor condition; 20th Century-Fox (Box 8)
  - Playhouse 90: Helen Morgan, 5/3/1957; 2266; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Carmichael, Hoagy; Bergen, Polly; Sidney, Sylvia (Box 8)
  - Playhouse 90: The Last Tycoon, 5/14/1957; 2040; 8x10, poor condition; Palance, Jack; Lindfors, Viveca (Box 8)
  - Playhouse 90: The Last Tycoon, 3/14/1957; 2041; 8xl0, poor condition; Lindfors, Viveca; Palance, Jack (Box 8)
  - Playhouse 90: The Ninth Day, 1/4/1957; 2250; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Laure, Piper; Dunn, James; Kerr, John (Box 8)
  - Plummer, Christopher, 2218; 7x9, good condition; Note on back (Box 8)
  - Plummer, Christopher, 2219; 7x9, good condition; Note on back (Box 8)
  - Pontiac Playwrights: Daisy, Daisy, 11/22/1956; 2213; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Ewell, Tom (Box 8)
  - Portia Faces Life, 10/20/1954; 2013; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Swenson, Karl (Box 8)
  - Portia Faces Life, 11/30/1954; 2518; 10x8, good condition; includes caption; Swenson, Karl; Carlon, Fran; Gillespie, Jean; MacManus, Ginger; Taylor, Charles (Box 8)
  - Portia Faces Life, 4/22/1954; 2646; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Taylor, Charles; Jarrett, Renne; Reid, Frances (Box 8)
  - Presidential National Conventions, 2556; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; five way split screen; Democratic National Convention; Republican National Convention (Box 8)
  - Preston, Wayde, 2350; 7x9, very poor condition (Box 8)
  - Pride of the Family, 11/12/1953; 2340; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Hyatt, Bobby; Hartman, Paul (Box 8)
  - Princeton '56, 2180; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Bogdonoff, Seymour; Princeton University (Box 8)
  - Producer’s Showcase: Caesar and Cleopatra, 2/1/1956; 2607; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Hardwicke, Cedric, Sir (Box 8)